A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1930
  - Mexico, 1930; 1930/323
    - Mexico - Carr, Henry P., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 338)
    - Mexico - Carr, Henry P., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 339)
    - Mexico - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 41, Folder 340)
    - BUS-1 Bustamente, Miguel E. Mexico: Notes re General Mortality of Part of Veracruz, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3736)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/323.E
      - Mexico, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 341)
    - Mexico - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/323.H
      - Mexico, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 341)
    - Mexico - Malaria, 1930; 1930/323.I
      - Mexico, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 341)
    - Mexico - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/323.O
      - Mexico, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 341)
  - Nicaragua, 1930; 1930/325
    - Nicaragua, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 342)
    - Nicaragua - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/325.E
      - Nicaragua, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 342)
    - Nicaragua - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/325.H
      - Nicaragua, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 342)
    - Nicaragua - Health Services, 1930; 1930/325.K
      - MAG-2 Magoon, Estus H. "Observations Concerning the Sewerage System of Managua", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3737)
  - Panama, 1930; 1930/327
    - Panama, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 343)
    - Panama - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/327.H
      - Panama, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 343)
    - Panama - Malaria, 1930; 1930/327.I
      - Panama, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 343)
      - SCH-1 Schapiro, Louis "Method of Identifying the Anopheles Mosquitoes of Panama", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3738)
    - Panama - Health Services, 1930; 1930/327.K
      - Panama, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Paraguay, 1930; 1930/329
    - Paraguay, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - Peru, 1930; 1930/331
    - Peru, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 344)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/331.E
      - Peru, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - El Salvador, 1930; 1930/333
    - El Salvador, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - Dominican Republic, 1930; 1930/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 345)
  - Venezuela, 1930; 1930/339
    - Venezuela, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 345)
    - Venezuela - Elmendorf, John E., 1930 (Box 42, Folder 346)
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 42, Folder 347)
    - Venezuela - Nursing, 1930; 1930/339.C
      - Venezuela, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 348)
    - Venezuela - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/339.H
      - Venezuela, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 348)
    - Venezuela - Malaria, 1930; 1930/339.I
      - Venezuela, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 348)
      - BEN-1 Benarroch, W. I. Malaria Investigations, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3739)
    - Venezuela - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/339.J
      - Venezuela, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 348)
  - Great Britain, 1930; 1930/400
    - Great Britain, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 349)
  - England, 1930; 1930/401
    - England - (A-G), 1930 (Box 42, Folder 349)
    - England - (H-S), 1930 (Box 43, Folder 350)
    - England - (T-Z) - Rothamsted Experimental Station, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 351)
  - Ireland, 1930; 1930/403
    - Ireland, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
    - Ireland - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/403.A
      - Ireland, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
    - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/403.E
      - Ireland, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - Australia, 1930; 1930/410
    - Australia, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
    - Australia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1930; 1930/410.D
      - Australia, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/410.E
      - Australia, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - South Australia, 1930; 1930/413
    - South Australia, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - New Zealand, 1930; 1930/418
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - Fiji, 1930; 1930/419
    - Fiji - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/419.H
      - Fiji, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Caribbean, 1930; 1930/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 353)
    - Caribbean - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/420.H
      - Caribbean Region, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Marquesas Islands, 1930; 1930/422
    - Marquesas Islands, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Belize, 1930; 1930/425
    - British Honduras, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Canada, 1930; 1930/427
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 43, Folder 354)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/427.A
      - Canada, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1930; 1930/427.C
      - Canada, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/427.E
      - Canada, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    - Canada - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/427.J
      - Canada, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    - Canada - Health Services, 1930; 1930/427.K
      - Canada, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/427.L
      - Canada - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Jamaica, 1930; 1930/437
    - Jamaica, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 357)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
    - Jamaica - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/437.H
      - Jamaica, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
    - Jamaica - Malaria, 1930; 1930/437.I
      - Jamaica, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
    - Jamaica - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/437.L
      - Jamaica, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
  - Ceylon, 1930; 1930/462
    - Ceylon, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
    - JAC-4 Jacocks, W. P. "Ceylon, Public Health Observations...", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3740)
    - Ceylon - Malaria, 1930; 1930/462.I
      - Ceylon, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
      - DYE-4 Dyer, Brian R. "Lime as a Diluent for Paris Green", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3741)
      - JAC-7 Jacocks, W. P. "Ceylon: notes on Malaria Control", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3742)
    - Ceylon - Health Services, 1930; 1930/462.K
      - DYE-5 Dyer, Brian R. "Ceylon - Final report ... July 30, 1927-August 6, 1930" (Box 555, Folder 3743)
  - Hong Kong, 1930; 1930/463
    - Hong Kong, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 358)
  - India, 1930; 1930/464
    - India - (A-M), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 359)
    - India - (N-Z), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 360)
    - JAC-3 Jacocks, W. P. "Observations re Public Health in Bombay" JAC-9 Jacocks, W. P. "Memorandum On a Visit to Punjab Province", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3744)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/464.E
      - India, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 360)
    - Kolar Taluk, 1930/464.I
      - MIE-1 Mieldazis, J. J. "Epidemic of Fever in Kolar Taluk", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3745)
    - India (Mysore), 1930; 1930/464.1
      - India - (Mysore) - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 361)
      - India - (Mysore), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 361)
    - India (Mysore) - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/464.1H
      - India - (Mysore), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 361)
    - India (Travancore), 1930; 1930/464.5
      - India - (Travancore) - Jacocks, W. P., 1930 (Box 44, Folder 362)
      - India - (Travancore) - Jacocks, W. P., 1930 (Box 44, Folder 363)
      - India - (Travancore) - Jacocks, W. P., 1930 (Box 44, Folder 364)
      - India - (Travancore) - (P-T), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 365)
      - India - (Travancore), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 365)
      - TAM-1 Tampi, K. Travancore Hookworm Survey, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3746)
    - India (Travancore) - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/464.5H
      - India - (Travancore), 1930 (Box 44, Folder 365)
      - TAM-1 Tampi, K. Travancore Hookworm Survey, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3746)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1930; 1930/466
    - Bengal, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 365)
    - JAC-11 Jacocks, W. J. "Report on Bengal Presidency", 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3747)
  - United Provinces, 1930; 1930/467
    - United Provinces, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 365)
    - JAC-8 Jacocks, W. J. "Memoranda on Public Health Organization in the United Provinces, India", 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3749)
    - United Provinces - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/467.J
      - Straits Settlements, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 366)
  - Malaysia, 1930; 1930/473
    - SCH-1 Scharff, J. W. Annual Report, 1928, 1930 (Box 555, Folder 3748)
  - South Africa, 1930; 1930/475
    - South Africa - Social Sciences, 1930; 1930/475.S
      - South Africa, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 366)
  - Kenya, 1930; 1930/476
    - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, Travel Awards, 1930; 1930/476.E
      - Kenya, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 366)
  - Mauritius, 1930; 1930/478
    - Mauritius, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 367)
    - ARI-1 d'Arifat, A. C. "Mauritius - Hookworm Report", 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3750)
  - North Africa Region, 1930; 1930/485
    - Egypt, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 367)
  - South Africa, 1930; 1930/487
    - South Africa, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 367)
    - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/487.E
      - South Africa, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 367)
  - France, 1930; 1930/500
    - France, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Taylor, R. M. and Hazemann, R. H. "Report of a Sanitary Survey of the Commune of Varennes-Sur-Seine", 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3751)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/500.E
      - France, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Algeria, 1930; 1930/501
    - Algeria, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Algeria - Malaria, 1930; 1930/501.I
      - Algeria, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - French Guiana, 1930; 1930/507
    - French Guiana, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Senegal, 1930; 1930/531
    - Senegal, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Senegal - Yellow Fever, 1930; 1930/531.O
      - Senegal, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Tunisia, 1930; 1930/539
    - Tunisia, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Tunisia - Malaria, 1930; 1930/539.I
      - Tunisia, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Tunisia - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/539.L
      - Tunisia, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Asia, 1930; 1930/600
    - Asia, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
    - Asia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/600.E
      - Asia, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - China, 1930; 1930/601
    - China - Administration, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 369)
    - China - Administration, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 370)
    - China - (A-G), 1930 (Box 45, Folder 371)
    - China - Grant, Dr. J. B., 1930 (Box 45, Folder 372)
    - China - Greene, R. S., 1930 (Box 45, Folder 373)
    - China - Greene, R. S., 1930 (Box 45, Folder 374)
    - China - (G-H), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 375)
    - China - (I-S), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 376)
    - China - (Su-V), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 377)
    - China - (W-Z), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 378)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/601.A
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Nursing, 1930; 1930/601.C
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/601.E
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Hookworm, 1930; 1930/601.H
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Malaria, 1930; 1930/601.I
    - China - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/601.J
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Health Services, 1930; 1930/601.K
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    - China - Public Health Education, 1930; 1930/601.L
      - China, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - Japan, 1930; 1930/609
    - Japan - (A-K), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 380)
    - Japan - (M-Z), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 381)
    - GRA-3 Grant, John B. "Japan, Public Health, Observations", 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3752)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/609.E
      - Japan - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 381)
  - Korea, 1930; 1930/613
    - Korea, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 382)
  - Thailand, 1930; 1930/617
    - Thailand (Siam), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 382)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/617.E
      - Thailand (Siam) - (A-Z), 1930 (Box 47, Folder 383)
  - Holland, 1930; 1930/650
    - Netherlands, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 384)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 384)
  - Java (Indonesia), 1930; 1930/655
    - HYD-3 Hydrick, J. L. Field Inspection Trips, Java, 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3753)
  - Sumatra, 1930; 1930/657
    - Sumatra, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 384)
  - Europe, 1930; 1930/700
    - Europe - (A-H), 1930 (Box 47, Folder 384)
    - Europe - (H-L), 1930 (Box 47, Folder 385)
    - Europe - (M-S), 1930 (Box 47, Folder 386)
    - Europe - (T-Z), 1930 (Box 47, Folder 387)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/700.A
      - Europe, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 387)
    - Europe - Public Health Demonstrations, 1930; 1930/700.J
      - Europe, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 387)
    - Europe - Health Services, 1930; 1930/700.K
      - Europe, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 387)
    - Europe - Humanities and Arts, 1930; 1930/700.R
      - Europe, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 387)
  - Austria, 1930; 1930/705
    - Austria, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 388)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/705.E
      - Austria, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 388)
    - Austria - Health Services, 1930; 1930/705.K
      - Austria, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 388)
  - Belgium, 1930; 1930/707
    - Belgium, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 388)
  - Yugoslavia, 1930; 1930/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 389)
    - HAC-5 Hackett, L. W. Trip through Yugoslavia, Bulgaria, Greece Report, 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3754)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 389)
  - Bulgaria, 1930; 1930/711
    - Bulgaria, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 389)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1930; 1930/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 390)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 390)
  - Denmark, 1930; 1930/713
    - Denmark, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 391)
  - Estonia, 1930; 1930/714
    - Estonia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 391)
  - Germany, 1930; 1930/717
    - Germany - (A-K), 1930 (Box 48, Folder 391)
    - Germany - (L-Z), 1930 (Box 48, Folder 392)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/717.E
      - Germany, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 392)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1930; 1930/717.S
      - Germany, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 392)
  - Hungary, 1930; 1930/750
    - Hungary, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 393)
    - Hungary - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/750.A
      - Hungary, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 393)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/750.E
      - Hungary, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 393)
  - Italy, 1930; 1930/751
    - HILL-6 Hill, Rolla B. Trip to Italy, Albania, Yugoslavia, and Bulgaria, 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3755)
      - Italy, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 394)
  - Liberia, 1930; 1930/759
    - Liberia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 394)
    - Liberia - Malaria, 1930; 1930/759.I
      - Liberia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 394)
  - Morocco, 1930; 1930/765
    - Morocco, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 394)
  - Norway, 1930; 1930/767
    - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Norway - Nursing, 1930; 1930/767.C
      - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/767.E
      - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Norway - Tuberculosis, 1930; 1930/767.T
      - Norway, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
  - Romania, 1930; 1930/783
    - Romania, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
    - Romania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/783.E
      - Romania, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
  - Russia, 1930; 1930/785
    - Russia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 395)
  - Latvia, 1930; 1930/786
    - Latvia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
    - Latvia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/786.E
      - Latvia, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
  - Finland, 1930; 1930/787
    - Finland, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
    - Finland - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/787.A
      - Finland, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/787.E
      - Finland, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
  - Poland, 1930; 1930/789
    - Poland, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 396)
  - Spain, 1930; 1930/795
    - HILL-2 Hill, Rolla B. Diary of a trip in Spain, 1930 (Box 556, Folder 3756)
  - Sweden, 1930; 1930/800
    - Sweden, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 397)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1930; 1930/800.A
      - Sweden, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 397)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/800.E
      - Sweden, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 397)
  - Switzerland, 1930; 1930/803
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Turkey, 1930; 1930/805
    - Turkey, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/805.E
      - Turkey, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Cyprus, 1930; 1930/809
    - Cyprus, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Palestine/Israel, 1930; 1930/825
    - Palestine, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
    - Palestine/Israel - Malaria, 1930; 1930/825.I
      - Palestine, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Syria, 1930; 1930/833
    - Syria, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
    - Syria, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
    - Syria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1930; 1930/833.E
      - Syria, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 398)
- General Correspondence, 1931
  - International, 1931; 1931/100
    - (F-H), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 399)
    - (I), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 400)
    - International - Nursing, 1931; 1931/100.C
      - (B-N), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 401)
    - International - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1931; 1931/100.D
      - Staff/International, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 402)
    - International - Hookworm, 1931; 1931/100.H
      - Staff/International, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 402)
    - International - Health Services, 1931; 1931/100.K
      - Staff/International, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 402)
    - International - Respiratory Diseases, 1931; 1931/100.M
      - Staff/International, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 402)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1931; 1931/100.O
      - (C-T), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 403)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1931; 1931/100.T
      - Trudeau Foundation, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 403)
  - United States, 1931; 1931/200
    - United States - (A-C), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 404)
    - United States - (D-H), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 405)
    - United States - (I-S), 1931 (Box 49, Folder 406)
    - United States - (T-W), 1931 (Box 50, Folder 407)
    - United States - (W-Z), 1931 (Box 50, Folder 408)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1931; 1931/200.A
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 409)
    - United States - Nursing, 1931; 1931/200.C
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 409)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/200.E
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 409)
    - United States - Malaria, 1931; 1931/200.I
      - United States - Cincinnati Institute - (A-L), 1931 (Box 50, Folder 410)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1931; 1931/200.L
      - United States - Cincinnati Institute - (M-W) - Vanderbilt University, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 411)
    - United States - Yellow Fever, 1931; 1931/200.O
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 412)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1931; 1931/200.R
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 412)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1931; 1931/200.S
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 412)
    - United States - Tuberculosis, 1931; 1931/200.T
      - United States, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 412)
  - Alabama, 1931; 1931/201
    - Alabama, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 413)
  - Arizona, 1931; 1931/203
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 413)
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 414)
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 415)
    - Arizona, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 416)
    - Arizona - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/203.E
      - Arizona, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 416)
    - Arizona - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1931; 1931/203.Q
      - Arizona, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 416)
  - Arkansas, 1931; 1931/204
    - Arkansas - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 417)
    - Arkansas - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1931 (Box 51, Folder 418)
    - Arkansas - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/204.E
      - Arkansas, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 418)
    - Arkansas - Malaria, 1931; 1931/204.I
      - Arkansas, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 418)
  - California, 1931; 1931/205
    - California - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 419)
    - California - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 420)
    - California - State Board of Health - (A-H), 1931 (Box 51, Folder 421)
    - California - (L-Z), 1931 (Box 51, Folder 422)
    - California - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1931; 1931/205.D
      - California, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 422)
    - California - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/205.E
      - California, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 422)
  - Colorado, 1931; 1931/207
    - Colorado, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Connecticut, 1931; 1931/208
    - Connecticut, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Florida, 1931; 1931/211
    - Florida, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Georgia, 1931; 1931/212
    - Georgia, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 424)
    - Georgia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/212.E
      - Georgia, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 424)
    - Georgia - Malaria, 1931; 1931/212.I
      - Georgia, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 424)
  - Hawaii, 1931; 1931/214
    - Hawaii, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 425)
  - Idaho, 1931; 1931/215
    - Idaho, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 425)
  - Illinois, 1931; 1931/216
    - Illinois, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 426)
    - Illinois - Nursing, 1931; 1931/216.C
      - Illinois, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 426)
  - Indiana, 1931; 1931/217
    - Indiana, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - Iowa, 1931; 1931/218
    - Iowa, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 427)
    - Iowa - Public Health Education, 1931; 1931/218.L
      - Iowa, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - Kansas, 1931; 1931/219
    - Kansas, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - Kentucky, 1931; 1931/220
    - Kentucky - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 428)
    - Kentucky - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 429)
    - Kentucky - (A-Z), 1931 (Box 52, Folder 430)
    - Kentucky - Malaria, 1931; 1931/220.I
      - Kentucky, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 430)
  - Louisiana, 1931; 1931/221
    - Louisiana - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 431)
    - Louisiana - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1931 (Box 52, Folder 432)
    - Louisiana - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/221.E
      - Louisiana, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 432)
    - Louisiana - Malaria, 1931; 1931/221.I
      - Louisiana, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 432)
  - Maine, 1931; 1931/222
    - Maine, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 433)
    - Maine - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/222.E
      - Maine, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 433)
  - Maryland, 1931; 1931/223
    - Maryland, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 433)
  - Minnesota, 1931; 1931/226
  - Mississippi, 1931; 1931/227
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 434)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 435)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 436)
    - Mississippi - (A-K), 1931 (Box 53, Folder 437)
    - Mississippi - (L-Z), 1931 (Box 53, Folder 438)
    - Mississippi - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1931; 1931/227.E
      - Mississippi, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 438)
      - Mississippi - Indianola Training Station, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 439)
    - Mississippi - Public Health Education, 1931; 1931/227.L
      - Mississippi - Indianola Training Station - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 54, Folder 440)